editorsdepot.com 2019-05-03

# 

###  Did we miss something? [Email](mailto:help@motionden.com) or [tweet us](https://twitter.com/@editorsdepot) and we will get back to you! 

At EditorsDepot, we know how critical it is to ensure the privacy rights and security of your personal information and we do everything we can to make sure that you are protected. 

This policy (together with our terms of use https://editorsdepot.com/terms-of-service and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. 

* * *

At EditorsDepot we have a few fundamental principles: 

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason). 
  * We never access any files in your account except to comply with the law. 
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products internally, or protect our rights 
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services. 
  * In our products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private and permanently deleted. 

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team. 

* * *

Website Visitors 

Like most website operators, EditorsDepot collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. EditorsDepot’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how EditorsDepot’s visitors use its website. From time to time, EditorsDepot may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

EditorsDepot also collects potentially personally-identifying information like internet protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and people viewing prototype URL’s. EditorsDepot only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below. 

* * *

Personal Information 

Certain visitors choose to interact with EditorsDepot in ways that require EditorsDepot to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that EditorsDepot gathered depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at editorsdepot.com to provide their name and email address. Those who engage in transactions with EditorsDepot — by purchasing access to our premium services or subscriptions for example — are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, EditorsDepot collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with EditorsDepot. Data relating to the transaction carried out through our site and the fulfillment of your orders will be stored. EditorsDepot does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them. Users have the right to data portability. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

* * *

Statistics 

EditorsDepot may collect statistics about the behavior of the visitors to its website. For instance, EditorsDepot may monitor the most popular templates on the editorsdepot.com site to see hur servers perform under the strain or analytics to measure where users spend their time in the platform. EditorsDepot may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, EditorsDepot does not disclose personally identifying information other than as described below. Additionally, EditorsDepot may monitor a website user's behavior and use that data customize EditorsDepot according to your individual interests. 

* * *

Protection of Personal Information 

EditorsDepot discloses potentially personal information only to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on EditorsDepot’s behalf or to provide services available at EditorsDepot’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using EditorsDepot’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. EditorsDepot will not rent or sell personal information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, EditorsDepot discloses potentially personal information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when EditorsDepot believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property rights of EditorsDepot, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of EditorsDepot and have supplied your email address, EditorsDepot may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with EditorsDepot and our products. We expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your feedback or to help us support other users. EditorsDepot takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personal information. All user data is kept private, except the user's name and avatar, which can be showed if the user has personally submitted a public review of our products. 

* * *

Access to information 

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. 

* * *

Cookies 

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. EditorsDepot uses cookies to help EditorsDepot identify and track visitors, their usage of EditorsDepot websites, and their website access preferences. EditorsDepot visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using EditorsDepot’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of EditorsDepot’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

EditorsDepot does not pre-screen content, but reserves the right (but not the obligation) in their sole discretion to refuse or remove any content that is available via the Service. 

* * *

Business Transfer 

If EditorsDepot, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the event that EditorsDepot goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the best assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of EditorsDepot may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy 

* * *

International Data Transfer 

EditorsDepot may potentially transfer user data internationally in order to provide a faster and more convenient user experience. For example, under the circumstance that a user is based in Australia, EditorsDepot may potentially transfer user data from United States to Australia in order to ensure that the user receives faster data load times. Whether data is transferred internationally or not, all data stored by EditorsDepot is protected by authenticated protocols and network firewalls. Internationally transferred data is also protected by authenticated protocols. 

* * *

Where we store your personal data 

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. 

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers, and data is delivered to you only over HTTPS, which is the most secure form of content delivery available. All financial transactions and details, such as your credit card number, are stored and processed on a third party payment service provider. You are responsible for keeping the password associated with your EditorsDepot account confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. 

* * *

Privacy Policy Changes 

Although most changes are likely to be minor, EditorsDepot may change it’s Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Ediot’s sole discretion. EditorsDepot encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to it’s Privacy Policy.
